<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<Computer id="dpa2_whitelist" name="Pacific_ATC_WhitelistAuthenticator" security="5" type="4" icon="Psylance">
  
  <!-- This whitelist server is 'unhackably secure', but the player can dig up the password to it on an earlier comp. 
  The player is here to sabotage the server to allow themselves access. I'm leaving this up to you and your narrative expertise,
  but I'm thinking we could include a file on here somewhere that's kind of a whitelist setup guide with instructions on how to add to the list via terminal.
  Also it should say you can only use this server via terminal.
  The command to add a line to the whitelist (this works in game) is:
  "append filename ip"
  so like this:
  "append list.txt 192.168.1.1"
  You need to be in the folder where the file exists for it to work of course.
  This mission is completable if the player adds their own IP to the whitelist or just crashes it's critical files, but I think it'll feel
  cooler if we hint at the player that they are supposed to add themselves onto it via files here.-->
  
  <portsForCrack val="5" />
  <ports>192, 9418</ports>
  <firewall level="-1"/>
  <proxy time="-1" />
  <trace time="80" />
  <portRemap>192=199</portRemap>
  <adminPass pass="CKYX258" />

  <WhitelistAuthenticatorDaemon SelfAuthenticating="false" />
  
  <positionNear target="dpa_bookings" position="180" total="360" extraDistance="0.15"/>

  <dlink target="dpa2_target" />

  <file path="home" name="whitelist_add.txt">To add a verified IP address to the server whitelist, insert the Schiss-Co License Dongle into your machine, making sure that you have enabled auto-run. The SLD contains a full suite of whitelist management software, but will only run on a licensed machine.

Alternatively, for systems that are firewalled, air-gapped, or otherwise unable to access public networks, consult list_add_manual.txt for instructions on manually adding IP addresses to your whitelist.</file>


  <file path="home" name="list_add.sys">#BINARY#</file>

  <file path="home" name="list_add_manual.txt">To manually add a verified IP address to your server whitelist, read thoroughly through the following instructions, making sure to double-check each command to ensure that no breaches of your network occur.

Note: this method is unsupported, and must be performed via terminal. Schiss-Co claims no liability on damages caused by use or misuse of these commands. For more information, consult your setup binder, supplied by your Schiss-Co representative.

Manually adding an IP address to your whitelist involves entering the terminal, navigating to the folder containing the whitelist, and appending your selected IP address to the whitelist file.

Step-by-step, the process goes like so:

1. Open the terminal. Schiss-Co recommendations: bash, xsh
2. Navigate to the folder containing your whitelist. By default, this is /home/whitelist.
3. Double-check the IP address to be added to your whitelist.
4. Append your selected IP by using the "append" command, followed by a space, your whitelist filename ("list.txt", in most cases), a second space, and your IP address. 

For example, if one wanted to add the "192.168.1.1" IP address to their whitelist, their terminal output might look like this:

whitelist-server:/ admin$ cd Whitelist
whitelist-server:whitelist admin$ append list.txt 192.168.1.1</file>


</Computer>