<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<mission id="Entropy_DLC_Connector">
  <goals>
    <!-- Impossible goal here - this mission isn't completable in the normal sense
    It leads the player to KaguyaTrials, which replaces this. We don't want the player
    to skip past this mission by quick replying or anything, so put a debug only goal here-->
    <goal type="getstring" target="kaguyatrialscompletedebug" />
  </goals>
  <missionStart val="1" suppress="true">addFlags:dlc_start_entropy</missionStart>
  <missionEnd val="1">addRank</missionEnd>
  <nextMission>NONE</nextMission>
  <posting title="#ALERT# - The Kaguya Trials"> ### CAUTION ###
Entropy Admins have flagged this contract as being unusually long, dangerous or difficult.
Unless you are very confident with your abilities, Admins suggest investigating this matter
at a later point.
 ### CAUTION ###
 
A hereto unknown agent has posted something of a recruitment challenge to leaders of a few groups. This is an open invite to investigate.
  </posting>
  <email>
    <sender>Entropy Mailbot</sender>
    <subject>The Kaguya Trials</subject>
    <body>Agent,
    
An individual named "Kaguya" has sent a challenge to, as far as we can tell, prominent DigiSec community leaders and administrators of various factions.
It looks like a recruitment challenge to form part of a team. As part of Entropy's openness policy, we're extending this invite to all interested parties.

Keep in mind that this is a separate group to Entropy, and will likely involve leaving this community for some time if you happen to join this other faction.
If you have unfinished business with Entropy, or wish to continue on your current path, it is very likely that this opportunity will still exist some time down the line - consider abandoning this contract and picking this thread up later if so.

Otherwise, the instructions given simply include an IP address (attached), and instructions to "Begin your trials".

Good luck,
-Entropy Admins
    </body>
    <attachments>
      <link comp="dKaguyaTrialIntro" />
    </attachments>
  </email>
</mission>