<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<Computer id="dPets_Engineer2" name="Ash-ALIENGEAR13" security="2" ip="54.192.234.65" icon="DLCPC2">

  <!-- Digipets artist - contains eos device hint for other comp  -->
  
  
  <dlink target="dPets_VC" />

  <positionNear target="dPets_MF" position="220" total="360" extraDistance="0.05"/>

  <file name="IMPORTANT_SusanLog.txt" path="home">

[S.Bonesau] No one's saying you HAVE to change your art style, just that...
[S.Bonesau] You do get an awful lot of requests for changes after submitting
[S.Bonesau] And I think we could improve efficiency if you took some of that more seriously
[S.Bonesau] As in, took previous feedback on board when planning future pieces.
[Ash] Ok I get that, but I really believe in this design
[S.Bonesau] I know. I understand, it's just...
[S.Bonesau] It's meant to be a spooky haunted house outfit, and you've drawn them all sitting in tanks
[S.Bonesau] Again.
[Ash] I like tanks. Tanks are scary.
[S.Bonesau] I know you like tanks
[Ash] You don't think the Romanians found the German tank lines scary?
[S.Bonesau] No, I mean, of course they did, that's beside the point, just hold on a sec
[Ash] That's 25 tonnes of German engineered death barreling down towards you, that's not spooky enough for you?
[S.Bonesau] Hold on!
[S.Bonesau] I just don't think our playerbase will connect with that the same way you do.
[S.Bonesau] Should I remind you that you also drew them all sitting in tanks for the fairy event?
[Ash] Tanks are a lot like fairies
[S.Bonesau] ...
[Ash] I like cute things and WW2 militaria, what do you want from me here?
[S.Bonesau] I want you to draw the DigiPets in Dracula costumes and stuff like that
[Ash] I'll do it if we can do a tanks event later
[S.Bonesau] This isn't really a bargaining situation for you
[Ash] I bet Dracula owned loads of tanks
[S.Bonesau] Jesus Christ, ok, deal, just draw the sprites
[Ash] I'm saving this log you know. It's happening.
[S.Bonesau] It's in my phone, don't worry
  </file>

  <file name="DRACULATANK.psd" path="home">#BINARY##BINARY#</file>
  <file name="asdf.psd" path="home">#BINARY#</file>
  <file name="asdf2.psd" path="home">#BINARY##BINARY#</file>
  <file name="asdfasdf.psd" path="home">#BINARY#</file>

  <!-- Memory dump with viewable sketches of Dracula tank -->
  <Memory>
    <Data>
      <Block>
STEAM_CHAT:activewindow
4e0f622c-c5f1-4959-902d-bd2c1009a4cb
Log:
CONSOLE: Never tell your password to anyone.
2:46 PM - Jigxor: these automaton videos are crazy
2:47 PM - Jigxor: oh man, I'm watching another one about a 240 year old automaton called 'the writer', which is a mechanical boy who can actually write out a whole sentence or two, with a real pen and paper in his hands, all mechanically driven with clockwork, this shit is unbelievable.
2:48 PM - Jigxor: and he's blinking and moving his head around and stuff
2:48 PM - [P]Ash: oh my god why did you put me onto these. I was going do get stuff done today ;_;
2:48 PM - Jigxor: it's crazy
CONSOLE: Jigxor Disconnected
CONSOLE: Jigxor Reconnected to Chat
3:18 PM - Jigxor: I feel smart
3:18 PM - Jigxor: even though I just copied some regex over from StackOverflow
3:18 PM - [P]Ash: >my_life.txt
      </Block>
    </Data>
    <Images>
      <Image>DLC/Sprites/Misc/DraculaTank</Image>
    </Images>
  </Memory>
  
  
</Computer>